The story begins in the dark forests of Middle Earth. Strider is hunting for the creature Gollum.
He tracks footsteps in the mud. The trail is fresh but dangerous.
The local villagers speak of a shadow growing in the East. Fear is spreading.
Strider enters the local tavern to gather information. The mood is tense.
He finds an Orc blade left behind. The enemy is closer than he thought.
The hunt continues into the night. Rain begins to fall heavily.
Strider lights a small fire, but quickly puts it out to avoid detection.
He hears a noise in the bushes. He draws his sword.
It was just a wild animal. He sheathes his blade and keeps moving.
Morning breaks. The sun reveals the path leading towards the mountains.
He spots Gollum in the distance, crawling near the riverbank.
Gollum senses he is being watched and flees into a cave.
Strider follows him into the darkness. The air is cold and damp.
Ambush! Orcs attack from the shadows. A battle begins.
Strider fights off three Orcs with skill and precision.
More enemies arrive. He is outnumbered but stands his ground.
He uses the environment to his advantage, trapping the Orcs.
The fight ends. Strider is wounded but victorious.
He tends to his wounds and resumes the pursuit of Gollum.
Gollum has escaped through a narrow tunnel. The trail has gone cold.
Strider climbs to a high vantage point to scan the horizon.
He spots smoke rising from a distant camp. Is it friend or foe?
He approaches the camp cautiously. It is a group of Elves.
The Elves offer him aid and information about the creature.
They warn him of the Nazgul searching for the Ring.
Strider leaves the Elves and heads towards the Dead Marshes.
The marshes are treacherous. One wrong step means death.
He sees faces in the water. The spirits of the dead are restless.
Finally, he catches Gollum in a snare trap.
Gollum struggles and curses "Baggins" and the "Precious".
Strider binds him and begins the long journey back.
The return journey is harder. The enemy knows he has the prisoner.
Orc riders appear on the horizon. A chase sequence begins.
They run through the forest, dodging arrows and blades.
Strider makes a stand at a narrow bridge to protect the prisoner.
He holds the bridge against the Orc captain. A duel ensues.
With a final strike, the Orc captain falls. The path is clear.
They reach the borders of the Elven lands. Safety is near.
He delivers Gollum to the dungeon of the Wood Elves.
The mission is complete. But the war for the Ring is just beginning.